opensourcescripts.com 2017-06-02

# Find Open Source Software Scripts CMS PHP ASP NET PERL CGI JAVA JAVASCRIPT

 Privacy Policy:

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should first contact Open Source Scripts via email (info @ opensourcescripts.com).

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. We do not sell or share any information that you submit. Please be aware that despite our best intentions, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Moreover, at times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest. 

Cookies   
A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. The use of cookies is now standard operating procedure for most Web sites. The cookie itself does not contain your personal information. Cookies do not damage your system.

Links  
OpenSourceScripts website contains links to other sites. OpenSourceScripts does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

IP Addresses  
OpenSourceScripts logs IP addresses for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes and to determine site usage. Your IP address does not contain personal information about you.

Your Consent  
By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy as specified above. OpenSourceScripts Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
